[
  {
    "front": "arrêter, s'arrêter",
    "back": "止"
  },
  {
    "front": "soi, auto-",
    "back": "自"
  },
  {
    "front": "rizière",
    "back": "田"
  },
  {
    "front": "ville, quartier",
    "back": "町"
  },
  {
    "front": "chien",
    "back": "犬"
  },
  {
    "front": "nouveau, neuf",
    "back": "新"
  },
  {
    "front": "vieux, ancien",
    "back": "古"
  },
  {
    "front": "nombreux, en grande quantité",
    "back": "多"
  },
  {
    "front": "en petit nombre, en petite quantité, un peu",
    "back": "少"
  },
  {
    "front": "tôt, de bonne heure",
    "back": "早"
  }
]
